听力测试。第一节，听下面五段短对话，每段对话后有一个小题，从题中所给的
,B It's raining again.
三个选项中选出最佳选项。听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。每段对话读两遍。
Will the school trip be put off?
Take it easy.
The radio says it'll be sunny later.
It's raining again.
Will the school trip be put off?
Take it easy.
The radio says it'll be sunny later.
I volunteer to tell stories to old people twice a week.
That sounds great and interesting.
I volunteer to help kids with schoolwork once a week.
What are your family rules,
Well, I must practice the guitar before dinner, and I have to help my mom make
breakfast every morning.
What are your family rules,
Well, I must practice the guitar before dinner, and I have to help my mom make
breakfast every morning.
The zoo is about five kilometers away from our school.
Five kilometers? The zoo is about five kilometers away from our
五，
Five kilometers? Yes!
第二节，听下面五段长对话或独白，每段对话或独白后有几个小题，从题中所给的三个选项中。选出最佳选项。听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间阅读各个小题，每小题五秒钟。听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。每段对话或独白读两遍。听第六段材料，回答。第六、七两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读下面两个小题。
kilometers zoo kilometers zoo about our
The zoo away zoo The Dave, now I'm ready.
Dave, I am going to travel to Australia.
May I ask you some questions about your country?
Sure, what do you want to know?
When you meet someone for the first time, what are you supposed to do?
We're supposed to shake hands.
I heard that you don't need to bring anything when you visit someone, is that true?
Oh no, it's polite to take some small gifts.
Taking a few flowers is a good choice.
Thanks, now I'm ready.
听第七段采。料，回答第八至第十三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读下面三个小题。
What a fine day today.
Let's play in the park this afternoon.
Good idea, we can skate there.
Yeah, skating is good exercise.
How can we get there?
We can take bus number four or the subway.
Um, taking the subway is more convenient.
How long will it take us to the
About 30 minutes.
Okay, when shall we meet?
At three o at the school gate.
Three o The park closes at six.
I think half past two is better.
Alright, see you later.
What a fine day today.
Let's play in the park this afternoon.
Good idea, we can skate there.
Yeah, skating is good exercise.
How can we get there?
We can take bus number four or the subway.
taking the subway is more convenient.
How long will it take us to the
About 30 minutes.
Okay, when shall we meet?
At three o at the school gate.
Three o The park closes at six.
I think half past two is better.
Alright, see you later.
听第八段材料，回答第十一。这第十三三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读下面三个小题。
Good afternoon. Can I help you?
Yes, it's Mother's Day tomorrow.
I'd like to buy some gifts for my mother.
Good. What about this dress?
Sorry, she doesn't like red.
Have you got any other colors?
Oh yes, we have also got blue, purple and white.
Can I have a look at the medium purple one?
Purple is my mother's favorite color.
Sure, here you are.
It looks nice.
How much is it?
Thirty -six dollars, but today is on sale.
You only need to pay half of the price now.
Okay. By the way, the white scarf looks great.
How much is it?
Eight dollars. Okay, I'll take them.
Good afternoon. Can I help you?
Yes, it's Mother's Day tomorrow.
I'd to buy some gifts for my mother.
Good. What about this dress?
Sorry, she doesn't like red.
Have you got any other colors?
Oh yes, we have also got blue, purple and white.
Can I have a look at the medium purple one?
Purple is my mother's favorite color.
Sure, here you are.
It looks nice.
How much is it?
Thirty -six dollars, but today is on sale.
You only need to pay half of the price now.
Okay. By the way, the white scarf looks great.
How much is it?
Eight dollars. Okay, I'll take them.
听第九段材料，回答第十四至第十六三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读下面。三个小题。嗨，
pay of the price now.
Hi, Maria. What's your favorite subject?
Math. Our math teacher is really fun.
What's your favorite subject?
I like English best.
Do you like English?
Well, I used to be good at English, but now I find it hard for me to study English
well. What are your difficulties in studying English?
I have trouble in memorizing the new words.
I often forget them.
I think you can copy them in a notebook and take it with you so that you can read
the words as often as you can.
Good idea. I'll have a try.
By the way, what about your listening?
It's weak. Sometimes I can't follow the speakers.
Well, you can watch English programs.
Thanks for your advice.
Hi, Maria. What's your favorite subject?
Math. Our math teacher is really fun.
What's your favorite subject?
I like English best.
Do you like English?
Well, I used to be good at English, but now I find it hard for me to study English
well. What are your difficulties in studying English?
I have trouble in memorizing the new words.
I often forget them.
I think you can copy them in a notebook and take it with you so that you can read
the words as often as you can.
Good idea. I'll have a try.
By the way, what about your listening?
It's weak. Sometimes I can't follow the speakers.
Well, you can watch English programs.
Thanks for your advice.
听第十段材料，回答第十七至第二十四个小题。现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读下面四个小题。
Good afternoon, dear judges.
My name is Tina.
I'm 15 years old.
It's my great honor to be here today.
My topic is my neighborhood.
I live in a big neighborhood.
In the middle of it, there is a beautiful park.
It's the biggest in our city.
Many people like to exercise in
are three restaurants on Spring Road.
Mike's is the best of all.
You can have the most delicious food there.
Next to the Mike's is the biggest supermarket, Smartway.
It's on right of our house, so many parents usually shop in it.
There are many different kinds of things in the supermarket, and most of them are
the newest in our city.
Wonderland is a bookstore.
on the other side of Spring Road.
It's modern and comfortable.
Welcome to my neighborhood.
That's all for my speech.
Thanks for your listening.
Good morning, dear judges.
My name is Tina.
I'm 15 years old.
It's my great honor to be here today.
My topic is my neighborhood.
I live in a big neighborhood.
In the middle of there is a beautiful park.
It's the biggest in our city.
Many people like to take exercise in it.
There are three restaurants on Spring Road.
Mike's is the best of all.
You can have the most delicious food there.
Next to Mike's is the biggest supermarket, Smartway.
It's on the right of our house, so my parents usually shop in it.
There are many different kinds of things in the supermarket, and most of them are
the newest in our city.
Wonderland is a bookstore.
It's on the other side of Spring Road.
It's modern and comfortable.
Welcome to my neighborhood.
That's all for my speech.
Thanks for your listening.
听力部分到此结束。